The subtitles in this video were written by hamburger Reika, the subtitle master, with table guitar by Cong στη.
I want to talk about the greatness of instrumental music!
Yay!
Yes. I'm Rio Sakurai from Morning Musume。' I'm Rio Sakurai of 23.
This time, too, I'd like to invite this person as a guest.
This is Riai Matsunaga from Juice-Juice.
Thank you very much.
Please give my best regards.
In the first part, I talked about the instrumental quality of three songs by Juice-Juice.
In the second part, I would like to introduce Morning Musume。 I would like to introduce songs by Morning Musume。
Thank you very much.
Well, how was it?
How was it?
It was fun, and I thought Riley's cheers were wonderful.
No, it wasn't. I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
So, let's start with the first song.
The first song is "Gyuusareta Dake Dake Dake Namera~.
This song is Morning Musume。 23 69th single.
It was released in December 2020.
The first point is the A melody.
The A-melody has the rhythm sound engraved, of course, but it is also easy to hear the synthesizer sound.
And also, the synthesizer sound is very audible.
This makes it easier to hear the synthesizer sound when singing, so I am using it as a reference.
I would like you to listen to it now. Please listen to it.
It's playing now.
The sound is quite distinctive, so it is easy to hear even with the chorus, so I think it would be interesting for everyone to compare the sound.
There are many songs that include synthesizer sounds, but this one is particularly easy to understand, so I hope you will listen to it.
I thought the line that came in the second time was really cool, and the synths were great.
The synths are great.
The synths are great. It's very exciting.
Next, there is a break in the song that lasts a little over 3 minutes and 5 seconds.
There is this break, and it stops for a moment.
The break stops for a split second and gives you goosebumps, so please listen to it. Please listen to it.
Thank you very much.
This part.
I really like the break at the end of the interlude, which I mentioned in the first part.
As I mentioned in the first part of the song, there is often a pattern of having an accent at the end of the interlude and then going into the chorus.
But in this song, I really like the break and the beginning of the chorus.
I really like the sound of the break.
I really like the sound of the break, and this break has lyrics in the actual cola side, but I like the sound of the break because it's instrumental.
I can play the sound of the break only in the instrumental version.
It's cool!
It's cool, isn't it?
It's something that really sounds completely different from Juice-Juice's music.
It's different, so I'm curious about the feeling when you sing it.
I wonder how they feel when they sing.
Indeed. We often sing instrumental versions of the songs at concerts.
Even when I sing in concert, I feel like I can hear quite detailed sounds in Morning Musume。 I feel like I can hear the fine sounds of Morning Musume。
I can hear the fine sounds of the music, and I can hear the rhythms and the frets of the songs.
I try to match the rhythm and the free time with those fine sounds.
There are a lot of sounds, especially in this song.
Cool!
That's great. Blake is cool.
Blake is cool.
Yes, it is. This Blake here is a very good guess point.
A point of recommendation.
So, I would like to roll the third one.
It's 3 minutes and 19 seconds long, and it's the "ochi-chi-chi-ni" (falling chorus).
There is a way to get excited only in Ochi-Sabi.
The pattern of "Ochi-Sabi" is that the song is grandiose all the way through, and the excitement builds up.
But in this "Gyuusare," the sound is really loud at one part.
But in this Gyusare, the sound is really loud in one part, and when the loud part is over, the song returns to a normal tone.
I think it would be easier if you listen to it.
guard
It's just a momentary sound, but this is where it really gets going. It's really cool.
I think the way the sound is carried is very interesting. I think it's interesting how the sound is carried.
How would you describe this moment in song?
I think it would be more powerful if you listen to it with a chorus, so I would like to hear it with a chorus.
You'll regret it later.
What? Scary!
I see.
After the part where it goes up, there's a thump, thump, thump, thump.
It's pretty impressive here.
Do you have absolute pitch?
Oh, no. Sorry. I made a mistake.
What is absolute pitch?
Not that. It's like if you hear a sound, you know the sound.
Relative pitch?
Relative?
I see. That's amazing.
Yes, it is. So, now that I have explained the three points... I have just introduced three points.
This song has a lot of sounds, and it is also very powerful.
And it has a lot of power, so even the instrumental version is very exciting.
So the instrumental version is also very exciting, and the chorus style gives it more power.
The chorus style makes it even more powerful, so I hope you will compare them.
I hope that you can compare the two songs.
Wow! Wow!
Let me introduce you to the new next one.
Let's see...
This is Morning Musume。 I'd like to introduce you to the next new song. The reason why I like this song is because I heard it at a concert of Hello! Project concert, Morning Musume。 Project concert, and I thought it was cool.
The first thing I like about this song is the piano before the chorus.
The first point I like is the piano before the chorus, which seems to be wandering around in my mind.
So, the sound delivery, the piano, even if I actually played it here, it really is wandering around all the time, isn't it?
So, I really feel like I'm wandering around, and I love it, so please listen to it now. Please listen to it.
Yes, the piano line right now, it's really wow-esque.
It's so fragile. So fragile! It's really ephemeral! I love this part so much that I even made my own piano extract soundtracks to listen to it.
I love this part so much that I've even made my own piano extracts and listen to them.
It's true, it's number 2, isn't it? Yes, there is a violin in the second verse! It's really wonderful, so please listen to it!It is indeed number 2. Yes, there is a violin in the second number! That part is really nice, so please listen to it, please.
That's it. Thank you for your hard work.
Yes, for now.
There's a violin going in.
I love to listen to this singer alone with headphones and booing!
It's nice. It's so crazy.
It's so cool.
This is where the violin comes in.
I love this song. I think it's from Morning Musume's last fall tour.
25th anniversary medley at the live performance.
That time.
When they were doing "Come on, body of the heart", this line was getting longer and longer.
I was going "wow" when I was watching it live.
Yume Kudo next to me was laughing all the time.
That Halloween...
But it's going to happen, isn't it?
It's so cool!
I love this place!
I love it here. The tune is really interesting, too.
but the choreography is so graceful to the sound of the piano.
I feel like I'm pulled into the world of the song.
I totally understand.
I love this part.
The next part is the chorus.
I love the piano and violin sound here.
I love the sound of the piano and the violin.
I love the piano and violin throughout the song.
There's the percussion part, right?
The violin sings along with the piano.
They sing together.
I'm jealous of that and love it.
That's how I feel.
The piano and the violin, and the part where he's rubbing his body.
and the violin in the part where he's rubbing his body
Please listen to the sound of the violin together
Please do!
Please also watch the next video!
More than here.
It's right here!
It's amazing!
The piano is so beautiful, but this, you know, violin...
I really like the part where he says, "The violin continues to walk the path of the violin. I love the way the violin is supporting the piano.
I love the feeling of being supported by the violin. And the accent before that is really cool, and I think the transition between the two is beautiful.
I love the part where he says, "Oh my God! I love the part where he says, "Oh my God!
The last part of the song, the last chorus, where there should have been a violin, is now just Pieno.
Yes. The lyrics are also linked.
I wonder, what does it mean?
Let's have a listen. Please listen to it.
[ED.
Borarop.
I see.
I see what you mean, what I was trying to say at this time.
Yes, the first turn of the last verse.
in the first turn of the last chorus.
In the last chorus, there was a violin with you, wasn't there?
But here it's just the piano.
So maybe this is the part where the main character
I guess I thought it was like the main character was ready to do something.
I was probably thinking that when I wrote this.
And the second chorus has a violin, too.
I think that's what I wanted to say at that time.
I knew you could tell by the change in the number of notes
I'm sure that's what you meant.
Shall we listen to it again?
Yes, please.
Next time
The timing of the violin makes it easier to ride the rhythm. The sound of the rhythm.
It's amazing.
The instrumentation is great.
Wow, it's very deep.
It's very deep.
It's great.
That's what I'm saying.
Thank you very much.
This is the last song already at an early stage.
Next, I would like to introduce Brainstorming.
Brainstorming is the 53rd single of Morning Musume。 13's 53rd single, released in April 2013.
Does that mean 10 years ago?
Yes, that's right.
What?
Just about 10 years ago.
The relationship between the break, the hit, and the accent was totally unpredictable.
It was one of those songs where you can't predict where the sound is going to get quieter or louder.
I like that very much, and it is a song based on electronic sounds, so I hope you will listen to it now.
I hope you will listen to what I am about to show you.
First of all, the first part of the song, "Do not play the frail maiden" is at 33 seconds.
The first one is the 33-second part where the song "A Weak Maiden Must Not Be Played," which is characterized by the small sound that gradually increases in volume.
The beat of the scale is very cool.
Do-do-do-do-do, do-do-do-do, la-sharp-so-sharp-so-sharp-so-sharp-so, and so on.
The scale goes up and down, so it's pretty easy to understand.
I think you can understand this scale even in the instrumental version, so I would be happy if you could listen to it.
Please listen to it.
So far, it's pretty easy to understand that the scale goes up and down.
With the chorus, the lyrics are in pitch, so I think it's very easy to understand.
I like the sound of the beat in the instrumental version, so I think this is my first recommendation.
I like to hear the sound of the beat in the instrumental, so this is my first point of recommendation.
I think it's easy to understand the lyrics, but I really like the sound of the beat in instrumental songs.
It's cool.
And, you know, it gets pretty exciting here.
I thought maybe a big sound was coming, but then it gets a little bit calmer again.I thought maybe a louder sound was coming, but then it got a little more subdued again.
Then, from the 56th second, the sound of "dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah" increases.
The scale goes down and up over and over again, and I really like it.
I really like that part, so I hope you will listen to it. Please listen to it.
It's a bit calm. This place is unique.
So far.
It's going up really fast at the moment, but it doesn't go to the chorus yet.
But it doesn't go to the chorus yet.
There is a lot of repetition.
I think the point of this song is that you can't predict when the chorus will come.
I think that's the point of this song.
It's amazing. I feel like the weight of the song has changed.
That's right.
It's like a "pop.
I think it gets really exciting before the chorus.
I really like that you can feel the excitement many times before the chorus.
Yes, it is.
And the third one.
The third one is at the 57-second mark.
I would like you to listen to it without the song.
The first thing I would like you to listen to is the song, but the notes are all connected by a slur in the piano symbol.
If you listen to the song, you will understand.
Please listen to the song.
The first school lunch is a fruit mask for endless
-Wait...wait...wait...wait...wait...wait...wait.
Recommendation
At the moment, the notes are connected with a slur that has been extended all the way through the mee-e-okire.
Oda-san is singing here.
If you listen to the instrumental version, the mee-o'-kire part is not connected to the rest of the song.
If you listen to the instrumental version, the mee-e-okire part is all "dong-dong-dong-dong" sounds.
The chorus is connected to the instrumental version, but the instrumental version is very cool because it sounds like a stand-alone song.
I would like you to listen to the instrumental version. I would like you to listen to the instrumental version.
Is it OK if I call it "konNAdo" or "konNAdo"?
I'm just going to say for now that it's a pretty intense sound.
It's a pretty intense sound, and there's a thump-thump-thump.
With singing, it's quite extended.
But in the production, you can really hear the sound on its own.
I can really feel it when I listen to the performance.
This is the third eagle point for me.
Even if you listen to the original song, you can feel the presence of the back sound in this part.
I hope you will listen to it.
Yes, I am very happy to hear it. That's how it ended.
Oh, wow!
That was amazing. And your handwriting in the script is so beautiful.
May I show it to you?
Is it okay?
Take a look.
It's just fine.
Can you see it?
No, no, no, no, no.
Look at it.
It's a very rough draft. Here.
Really? It looks like my handwriting.
Did you see it?
It doesn't matter what you write as long as you can read it.
It's amazing. Look.
It's amazing. He's the same age as you.
High school senior?
The same age?
That's amazing.
It was a lot of fun.
I am so glad that there are people who can share and talk about the fun and depth of this event with me.
Thank you very much.
I thought that Riley and I would talk more about instrumentation, even if it wasn't for this project.
I would like to talk more about instrumental music with Riley, even if it is not for this project.
I would also like to share more about how much I like this song with Riley.
I would like to do that.
I would like to share more with Riley about how much I like this song.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. So, as you can see.
I have introduced 6 songs in total for the first part and the second part.
Yay!
We have introduced a lot of our points, so please listen to them.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye Riley!
I'll do it with a bang. That's so cool. And when is your birthday? My birthday is November 11th.
What, November 11? That's a really big number. That's right. I'm July 7, so I'm on the same side of the zodiac as you.
Oh, that's right. What is your favorite number? My favorite number is 8.
8. 8? Why? I don't know. Do you know what a home bakery is? A home bakery?